

jessica f. jin

UX/UI DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

experience

Marketing Designer & Developer 2016-2017 Codify Academy

- Designed and developed 10+ user facing websites and applications for different clients
- Managed creative projects from concept to completion shaping brands, stories, and strategy
- Spearheaded marketing efforts leading to a 30% leads increase, 10% sales increased, and increased inter-department communication
- Mentored younger developers new to coding

Associate Consultant Triage Consulting Group

2014-2016

- · Presented and created weekly, monthly, and quarterly status reports to teams of 2-20
- Sustained and closed 800+ accounts tracking risk
- Researched 8K+ claims to identify upcoming trends
- Recovered \$100M+ in unrealized revenue

Strategic Data Analyst Makeda Capital, LCC

Spring 2015

• Drove research and informed investment decisions for portfolio of 71 female Fortune 500 companies

education

BA in Human Biology **Stanford University**

2010-2014

Program in Nonprofit Design

Spring 2013

University of Cape Town

skills

HTML5/CSS3

Sketch

iQuery

Flinto

Bootstrap

JavaScript

Lean UX

• UI Design

SQL

MS Access

www.jessfjin.com 770 Van Ness Ave SF, CA

profile

408-306-7689 Phone

professional summary

Creative, action-oriented, outside-the-box

digital storytelling to help my client's brands

management, research, and data analysis.

to exceeding expectations, leading and

into the deep end and get things done!

Accustomed to wearing multiple hats in fast-

motivating teams, and achieving the goals of

socially-conscious organizations. Ready to dive

paced environments. Always learning, committed

stand out. 6+ years of experience in strategic marketing, branding, client services, project

thinker with expertise in UX and graphic design. Excited to stretch boundaries of web design and

Email jessica.f.jin@gmail.com

Website

Address